https://www.catcomtec.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Catalyst Communication Technologies
You are here:
Home/ Privacy Policy
Search
See below our privacy policy. By browsing our site you agree to these terms and conditions.
PRIVACY STATEMENT
This statement applies to use of personal information obtained via websites operated by Catalyst Communications Technologies, Inc. (“Catalyst”).
USE OF INFORMATION
Catalyst collects personal information you voluntarily choose to provide such as your name, address, email address, phone numbers.
Catalyst may use the personal information for marketing, research and administration purposes, including but not limited to, facilitating order processing; to contact you by telephone or email for marketing and promotion of Catalyst products and services; to facilitate the employment application process; or for other uses consistent with this statement.
Catalyst does not provide your personal information to third parties except for third party business partners who provide services to Catalyst that are consistent with this Statement and our website, or as a part of a specific product, service, marketing or promotion.  In addition, Catalyst may disclose personal information if we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
Catalyst does NOT collect unsolicited proprietary and confidential information such as social security numbers, credit card, or other electronic payment information through its website.  Please be advised that any unsolicited information that is communicated using the Catalyst website will be considered to be, and treated as, non-confidential and non-proprietary.
HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED
IP ADDRESSES
Catalyst may at any time log your IP address when you access the Catalyst website. This IP address generally does not reveal your identity to Catalyst.
COOKIES
Catalyst may place information on your computer to allow Catalyst to identify you in the form of a “cookie”. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many websites use them. You have choices with respect to cookies. By changing your internet browser preferences, you have the ability to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. Please note that, if you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those services or engage in activities that require the placement of cookies.
ONLINE ADVERTISING
Catalyst uses third party vendors, including Google, to display advertising on other websites across the internet.  These third party vendors may use cookies to track and target advertising based on your browsing behavior.  Catalyst has no control over how these third party vendors may collect or use your personal information.
WEB BEACONS
Catalyst may use small files to count the number of unique users that have visited a specific page on the web site. This information is generally not linked to any personally identifiable information.
SECURITY DISCLAIMER
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT INTERNET COMMUNICATION MAY NOT BE SECURE AND THAT CATALYST CANNOT AND DOES NOT WARRANT THAT YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WILL NOT BE DISCLOSED OR ACCESSED BY PARTIES OTHER THAN THOSE AUTHORIZED UNDER THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. YOU AGREE THAT CATALYST WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR SUCH DISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION.
16 Oct
Catalyst
@catcomtec
A new White Paper to help explain why Interworking between LMR and LTE public safety users needs to be based upon standards, and the dangers of using proprietary Push to Talk over cellular services, can now be downloaded from the Catalyst website.
blog.catcomtec.com/2020/10/16…
12 Oct
Catalyst
@catcomtec
There's a new post up on the Catalyst Blog about our participation in the ETSI sponsored Plugtest and our successful integration of our Mission Critical Push to Talk technology with other vendors' products for new LTE based services. Check it out HERE: blog.catcomtec.com/2020/10/09…
25 Aug
Catalyst
@catcomtec
Lots of great energy and connections at Virtual IWCE. Check out the Catalyst Virtual booth: pic.twitter.com/gevor4LWOZ
20 Aug
Catalyst
@catcomtec
@AdvaMobile First Steps for New Adva Mobile Subscribers
youtube.com/watch?v=tQyrt4…
20 Aug
Catalyst
@catcomtec
The fourth product highlight at Virtual IWCE next week is Dispatch. Check out a preview here:
youtube.com/watch?v=hc0P-7…
Be sure to check out Catalyst next week at the Virtual IWCE Trade show, and use WELCOME10 when you register for a Free Pass to the Virtual Exhibit Hall.
Footer Section
ResourcesPress Releases
Articles
Events
Videos
Industries
Company Address :
2107 Graves Mill Road, Mail Stop D, Forest, VA 24551 *
Map
*
Phone :
1 (434) 582-6146 *
Support :
